[Music]
I'm Rob jolof I'm president of saber
limited saber limited is a Microsoft
Dynamics business Central partner
located in Ontario Canada focused
exclusively on manufacturing anywhere in
North
America business Central is one of the
fastest growing Erp systems in the cloud
today and that growth is causing a
problem where there just aren't enough
talented people in the ecosystem to
support that
growth business Central is a new
technology we need a new mindset we need
a new perspective and Millennials and
younger people are bringing that
perspective in the business Central
Community and what saber needs we need
we need digital natives we need people
who are used to technology they grew up
with it and it's natural and they have
experience in
Industry saber has been trying to do a
program like res skill on our own for
quite some time and and res skill just
came along it it is actually the right
program for us it helps fill the talent
Gap two months to have res skill find
that candidate was about what it might
have taken us but the effort was much
much less for
us the most valuable component of res
skill is the training and coaching we're
very likely to send a couple of our
internal staff on the res skill program
for the training and coaching because
it's just going to add a lot of value
it's going to give them some experience
and expertise they need
the fact that res skill is combining
both the recruiting and the training and
onboarding and mentoring of those
candidates is a huge advantage and a
great value I think res skill would be a
great program for partner who wants to
upskill their existing staff or hire new
staff